mywifeashley.com 2018-08-24

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy applies to the following website: www.mywifeashley.com (“Site”). 

We are totally committed to protecting your privacy and security. The following information is designed to help you understand how we collect, use, disseminate and safeguard the information you provide to us while accessing and using our Site. By accessing and using our Site, you signify your assent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with our information practices, please do not access or use our Site. As provided below, we reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, add or remove portions of this policy at any time by posting such changes to this page. Such changes will be effective upon posting. The Site requests that you read this Privacy Policy carefully and consult it regularly. 

Information Collection and Use 

A. Information Collection. When users order our services, the payment processor collects information such as names, billing addresses, telephone numbers, email addresses, and credit card numbers. We collect information from our users when the user signs on to our Birth Date Verifier™ script, enters account information, uses our payment processing page, and uses/orders/purchases our services. Information is collected through completion of on-line forms on the join page and in the online store and sent to our payment processor for credit card verification. If a user refuses to provide the required information for a specific service, the user will not be able to utilize that service. 

B. Information Use. We use information for the following purposes: to fulfill your requests for services, to process credit card payments, to answer billing questions, to reset user names, and to contact you. We reserve the right to use your information for market research data purposes to increase the user’s experience according to personal interests and to formulate statistical models to accomplish the Site’s goals through surveys or contests. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others. 

Registration and Order Forms

To use, purchase, or order services on our Site, a user must complete an on-line form. The form requires a user to provide us (and our payment processor) with certain contact information (including, but not limited to, your name, mailing address, telephone number, and e-mail address) and certain financial information (including your credit card number and the expiration date for your credit card). This information is used to purchase services, verify credit card details, validate credit identity, and/or manage the user’s account. If we have trouble processing an order or otherwise need to contact a user, the contact information is used to get in touch with the user. From time to time, we may also ask that you provide us with additional information so that we can better tailor our services to meet your needs. 

Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive when the user visits certain Web sites and contains information about the user. We will not use cookies to collect personal identification information from our users. However, we will use cookies and traffic reporting software to log referral URL’s and browser preferences. Please note that some of our business partners may also use cookies on our Site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

Sharing and Third Party Distribution of Information

We do not currently sell, distribute, or otherwise make available personally identifiable information about our users to third parties. Nevertheless, we reserve the right to make such information available to third parties in the future in order to enhance and personalize our services, or in the case of bankruptcy, sale of an asset, business or division, a merger or acquisition, or similar change of ownership. This Site also makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, clubs, and/or news groups available to our users. Please remember that information disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

Law Enforcement

We will cooperate with law enforcement authorities, private-party litigants, and others seeking information about our end users to the extent required by applicable law. Examples of such cooperation include compliance with discovery requests, subpoenas, court orders and writs. 

Links

The Site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware that when they leave our Site they should read the privacy statements of each and every site that collects personally identifiable information. 

Security

We agree to use commercially reasonable efforts to protect the information you have provided to us from unauthorized access by using encryption and other security measures. All credit information is transmitted via a secured server through CCBill for membership purchases. We encourage you to visit CCBill’s website and CCBill’s privacy policy regarding its privacy policies. Although we take reasonable efforts to make our network secure, the Site cannot guarantee that the security measures in place will stop third-party “hackers” from illegally accessing your information. We encourage you to contact us if you are interested in learning more about our security measures. 

Children

Our Site is not intended for children under the age of 18 or 21, depending on the age of majority in your jurisdiction. Our Site does not target children, nor do we solicit data, or knowingly collect personally identifiable information from them. We encourage parents and legal guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate in the interactive activities offered on the sites their children visit. 

Data Quality, Access, and Updating Personal Information

The Site will take reasonable steps to ensure that the Site’s information and data is complete, accurate, and timely for the user’s desired purposes. If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as phone number or a credit card number), is inaccurate, or if a user no longer desires our services, the user should contact us to correct or update the information. 

Information Retention

Our payment processor retains all users’ information in a secure database. 

Newsletters, Correspondence, and Opt-out Policy 

We reserve the right to send our users and advertisers e-mail or other notices regarding new services, promotions, or other information which may be of general interest. Advertisers and users who no longer wish to receive materials from us may opt-out of receiving these communications by choosing an “unsubscribe” option or by contacting us. We will comply will all requests for removal. 

Notification of Changes

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting such changes on our Site. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective upon posting such changes. If you access or use our Site, you are required to periodically check our Privacy Policy for any changes. If you continue to access or use our Site after we have changed our Privacy Policy, you manifest your assent to the changes to our Privacy Policy. 

If we decide to use your personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated in the Privacy Policy at the time that such information was collected, we will attempt to notify you of such changes. You agree that if we send you an e-mail to the e-mail address reflected in our records, such e-mail will constitute acceptable notice to you of the change in our policy. The notice will provide you with an opportunity to “opt-out” so that we may not use your personally identifiable information in a manner which is different from the manner described at the time that you provided us with such information. If you do not affirmatively “opt-out” pursuant to the instructions provided to you in the notice, then you agree that we may use your personally identifiable information in the manner described in the notice. (If we have no e-mail address for you, or if we do not have a current e-mail address for you, then you agree that adequate notice of the change in our policy will be effected by posting such a change onto our Privacy Policy, which shall also disclose information about how you may “opt-out” so that we may not use your personally identifiable information in a manner which is materially different from the manner described at the time that you provided us with such information. If you do not affirmatively “opt-out” pursuant to the instructions posted within the time period specified, then you agree that we may use your personally identifiable information as described in the posted notice). 

Contact Information

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, you can contact us by sending an e-mail. Please provide us with your name and e-mail address so we can service you quicker.

Please send your e-mail to: naughtyathome@aol.com

This document was prepared by Lawrence G. Walters, Esq., of www.FirstAmendment.com.
